<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:19:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Decarbonization has a Natural Gas Pipeline Problem</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</guid>
      <description>A disorderly, market-based process to reduce greenhouse gases by removing appliances that burn natural gas from every home and building in the United States has begun. This strategy, such as it is, intends to replace appliances that use natural gas with ones that use electricity from more renewables and other carbon free energy sources over time. Most policy advocates and community groups today are focused on the appliance aspects of the transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Count Utility Shutoffs, Ban Them</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 18:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Sesame Street from YouTube
  We&amp;rsquo;re taught to count things from an early age and for some, like our childhood friend here, counting can become an obsession. But obsession or not, counting is a fundamentally useful form of information. As a policy advocate grounded in engineering training, more information is valuable when that information fills in a gap in my knowledge, and becomes necessary if filling that gap in my knowledge will fundamentally change a decision I would otherwise make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Biden: Fund Utilities, Defund Police</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Karolina Grabowska from Pexels
  This week Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s White House announced that the President would encourage mayors and governors - or &amp;ldquo;cities and states&amp;rdquo; - around the country to use unspent American Rescue Plan Act (ARPA) dollars to fund police. Not rent relief. Not utility debt relief. Not supplement food assistance. Not even public transit to relieve gas price pressures. More police. And they did it while hinting that it&amp;rsquo;s to provide funding for more cops and overtime pay for those cops to tamp down protest in the summer of 2022, relying on falsified reports about made-up &amp;ldquo;crime wave&amp;rdquo; stories to gin up support for more police.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving No One Behind While Multisolving for a Just Recovery</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/leaving-no-one-behind-while-solving-for-a-just-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 12:36:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/leaving-no-one-behind-while-solving-for-a-just-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Gustavo Fring from Pexels
  Everyone is worried about the contagion of coronavirus as cases skyrocket. And we should be. Its growth is out of control, and it is killing thousands every day. We can&amp;rsquo;t afford, however, to let that obscure an equally alarming disease of poverty and homelessness. Just as we all have been forced to shelter in place because some of us are sick, none of us will be spared from these more structural threats to our health and the long-term future for our planet&amp;rsquo;s habitability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
