<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>COVID-19 on isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/tags/covid-19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in COVID-19 on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:44:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>President Biden: Fund Utilities, Defund Police</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 14:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Karolina Grabowska from Pexels
  This week Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s White House announced that the President would encourage mayors and governors - or &amp;ldquo;cities and states&amp;rdquo; - around the country to use unspent American Rescue Plan Act (ARPA) dollars to fund police. Not rent relief Not utility debt relief. Not supplement food assistance. Not even public transit to relieve gas price pressures. More police. And they did it while hinting that it&amp;rsquo;s to provide funding for more cops and overtime pay for those cops to tamp down protest in the summer of 2022, relying on falsified reports about made-up &amp;ldquo;crime wave&amp;rdquo; stories to gin up support for more police.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving No One Behind While Multisolving for a Just Recovery</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/leaving-no-one-behind-while-solving-for-a-just-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 12:36:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/leaving-no-one-behind-while-solving-for-a-just-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Gustavo Fring from Pexels
  Everyone is worried about the contagion of coronavirus as cases skyrocket. And we should be. Its growth is out of control, and it is killing thousands every day. We can&amp;rsquo;t afford, however, to let that obscure an equally alarming disease of poverty and homelessness. Just as we all have been forced to shelter in place because some of us are sick, none of us will be spared from these more structural threats to our health and the long-term future for our planet&amp;rsquo;s habitability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
