<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>COVID-19 on isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/tags/covid-19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in COVID-19 on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:59:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Joins France to Ban Utility Shutoffs Permanently</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/los-angeles-bans-utility-shutoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/los-angeles-bans-utility-shutoffs/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Manya Krishnaswamy from Unsplash
Utility shutoffs are still the law of the land, but for how much longer? In December 2022, Los Angeles organizers won a multi-year fight against utility debt and for utility shutoffs within the largest public utility in the country, the Los Angeles Department of Water and Power, which serves over 4 million households and businesses in its service territory.
With this definitional change in shutoff policy, governance at the U.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden: Fund Utilities, Defund Police</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Karolina Grabowska from Pexels
This week Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s White House announced that the President would encourage mayors and governors - or &amp;ldquo;cities and states&amp;rdquo; - around the country to use unspent American Rescue Plan Act (ARPA) dollars to fund police. Not rent relief. Not utility debt relief. Not supplement food assistance. Not even public transit to relieve gas price pressures. More police. And they did it while hinting that it&amp;rsquo;s to provide funding for more cops and overtime pay for those cops to tamp down protest in the summer of 2022, relying on falsified reports about made-up &amp;ldquo;crime wave&amp;rdquo; stories to gin up support for more police.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
