<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>utilities on isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/tags/utilities/</link>
    <description>Recent content in utilities on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:28:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/tags/utilities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Utility Justice Reading List</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/a-utility-justice-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:28:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/a-utility-justice-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>In October, i published a new curriculum to aid organizers across the country to better understand the history of the electric utility system and to teach the history to others. My great hope is that it helps deepen our collective understanding of energy and, specifically, electric utility systems.
From doing the research that shaped the curriculum&amp;rsquo;s final contents, i read more than two dozen different texts. Some were more influential than others, and i&amp;rsquo;ve been asked to share a short reading list as a deeper introduction to utility justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Need Public Power for Energy Equity</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/we-need-public-power-for-energy-equity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 14:46:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/we-need-public-power-for-energy-equity/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Arch Solar from YouTube
If we want to create an equitable future for electricity in the United States, we have to expand public ownership of the electricity system rapidly and comprehensively. With more than one-quarter of all U.S. households currently experiencing deep energy insecurity, private ownership of generation and the grid and the requirement of private utilities to produce competitive profits for their investments is not only insufficient for the tasks ahead under any rapid decarbonization scenario, it is fundamentally opposed to the equally urgent tasks of resisting energy apartheid as we green the power sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Decarbonization has a Natural Gas Pipeline Problem</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</guid>
      <description>A disorderly, market-based process to reduce greenhouse gases by removing appliances that burn natural gas from every home and building in the United States has begun. This strategy, such as it is, intends to replace appliances that use natural gas with ones that use electricity from more renewables and other carbon free energy sources over time. Most policy advocates and community groups today are focused on the appliance aspects of the transition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Count Utility Shutoffs, Ban Them</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 18:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Sesame Street from YouTube
We&amp;rsquo;re taught to count things from an early age and for some, like our childhood friend here, counting can become an obsession. But obsession or not, counting is a fundamentally useful form of information. As a policy advocate grounded in engineering training, more information is valuable when that information fills in a gap in my knowledge, and becomes necessary if filling that gap in my knowledge will fundamentally change a decision I would otherwise make.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden: Fund Utilities, Defund Police</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Karolina Grabowska from Pexels
This week Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s White House announced that the President would encourage mayors and governors - or &amp;ldquo;cities and states&amp;rdquo; - around the country to use unspent American Rescue Plan Act (ARPA) dollars to fund police. Not rent relief. Not utility debt relief. Not supplement food assistance. Not even public transit to relieve gas price pressures. More police. And they did it while hinting that it&amp;rsquo;s to provide funding for more cops and overtime pay for those cops to tamp down protest in the summer of 2022, relying on falsified reports about made-up &amp;ldquo;crime wave&amp;rdquo; stories to gin up support for more police.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
