<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>utilities on isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/tags/utilities/</link>
    <description>Recent content in utilities on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 18:04:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/tags/utilities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Count Utility Shutoffs, Ban Them</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 18:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Sesame Street from YouTube
  We&amp;rsquo;re taught to count things from an early age and for some, like our childhood friend here, counting can become an obsession. But obsession or not, counting is a fundamentally useful form of information. As a policy advocate grounded in engineering training, more information is valuable when that information fills in a gap in my knowledge, and becomes necessary if filling that gap in my knowledge will fundamentally change a decision I would otherwise make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Biden: Fund Utilities, Defund Police</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 14:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/fund-utilities-defund-police/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Karolina Grabowska from Pexels
  This week Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s White House announced that the President would encourage mayors and governors - or &amp;ldquo;cities and states&amp;rdquo; - around the country to use unspent American Rescue Plan Act (ARPA) dollars to fund police. Not rent relief. Not utility debt relief. Not supplement food assistance. Not even public transit to relieve gas price pressures. More police. And they did it while hinting that it&amp;rsquo;s to provide funding for more cops and overtime pay for those cops to tamp down protest in the summer of 2022, relying on falsified reports about made-up &amp;ldquo;crime wave&amp;rdquo; stories to gin up support for more police.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
