<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>policy on isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/tags/policy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in policy on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:19:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/tags/policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Decarbonization has a Natural Gas Pipeline Problem</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</guid>
      <description>A disorderly, market-based process to reduce greenhouse gases by removing appliances that burn natural gas from every home and building in the United States has begun. This strategy, such as it is, intends to replace appliances that use natural gas with ones that use electricity from more renewables and other carbon free energy sources over time. Most policy advocates and community groups today are focused on the appliance aspects of the transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Count Utility Shutoffs, Ban Them</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 18:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Sesame Street from YouTube
  We&amp;rsquo;re taught to count things from an early age and for some, like our childhood friend here, counting can become an obsession. But obsession or not, counting is a fundamentally useful form of information. As a policy advocate grounded in engineering training, more information is valuable when that information fills in a gap in my knowledge, and becomes necessary if filling that gap in my knowledge will fundamentally change a decision I would otherwise make.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
