<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>climate on isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/tags/climate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in climate on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:19:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/tags/climate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Decarbonization has a Natural Gas Pipeline Problem</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:19:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/building-decarbonization-has-a-natural-gas-pipeline-problem/</guid>
      <description>A disorderly, market-based process to reduce greenhouse gases by removing appliances that burn natural gas from every home and building in the United States has begun. This strategy, such as it is, intends to replace appliances that use natural gas with ones that use electricity from more renewables and other carbon free energy sources over time. Most policy advocates and community groups today are focused on the appliance aspects of the transition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving No One Behind While Multisolving for a Just Recovery</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/leaving-no-one-behind-while-solving-for-a-just-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 12:36:59 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/leaving-no-one-behind-while-solving-for-a-just-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Gustavo Fring from Pexels
Everyone is worried about the contagion of coronavirus as cases skyrocket. And we should be. Its growth is out of control, and it is killing thousands every day. We can&amp;rsquo;t afford, however, to let that obscure an equally alarming disease of poverty and homelessness. Just as we all have been forced to shelter in place because some of us are sick, none of us will be spared from these more structural threats to our health and the long-term future for our planet&amp;rsquo;s habitability.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
