<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>abolition on isaac sevier</title>
    <link>https://isaacsevier.com/tags/abolition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in abolition on isaac sevier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 19:25:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://isaacsevier.com/tags/abolition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Writing a Utility Justice Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/on-writing-a-utility-justice-curriculum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 19:25:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/on-writing-a-utility-justice-curriculum/</guid>
      <description>After more than six years of working on energy policy in California and across the country, one of the things that was missing from every flavor of conversation about energy equity or justice or democracy that i was a part of was a shared level of knowledge as a foundational starting point. I was invited into and leading discussions in room after room where sometimes it felt like we couldn&amp;rsquo;t make any progress together because of a whole host of assumptions and varying levels of knowledge that everyone carried into the room and couldn&amp;rsquo;t communicate clearly enough to one another in 60 minutes or less (or 25 minutes after a 35 minute ice breaker).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Utility Justice Reading List</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/a-utility-justice-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:28:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/a-utility-justice-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>In October, i published a new curriculum to aid organizers across the country to better understand the history of the electric utility system and to teach the history to others. My great hope is that it helps deepen our collective understanding of energy and, specifically, electric utility systems.
From doing the research that shaped the curriculum&amp;rsquo;s final contents, i read more than two dozen different texts. Some were more influential than others, and i&amp;rsquo;ve been asked to share a short reading list as a deeper introduction to utility justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Count Utility Shutoffs, Ban Them</title>
      <link>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 18:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://isaacsevier.com/notes/ban-utility-shutoffs/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Sesame Street from YouTube
We&amp;rsquo;re taught to count things from an early age and for some, like our childhood friend here, counting can become an obsession. But obsession or not, counting is a fundamentally useful form of information. As a policy advocate grounded in engineering training, more information is valuable when that information fills in a gap in my knowledge, and becomes necessary if filling that gap in my knowledge will fundamentally change a decision I would otherwise make.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
